Lamp in the resert research files, ca. 1958-1960
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Lamp in the desert research files, ca. 1958-1960
AZ 065
Martin, Douglas D. (Douglas DeVeny), 1885-1963
Collection consists of author's original drafts and printer's copy, accompanied by notes, audio tape recordings and other research material. Includes historical accounts of various university departments written by others and which did not appear in the published version.
1.7 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Douglas D. Martin, author of The Lamp in the Desert, was an author, newspaperman, and member of the University of Arizona journalism faculty, 1946 to 1956.
Organization
This collection is organized into three series:
Series I: Manuscript Drafts, 1960
Series II: Audiotapes and Transcripts, 1958-1960
Series III: Historical Accounts, 1958-1960
Scope and Content Note
Collection consists of author's original drafts and printer's copy, accompanied by notes, audio tape recordings and other research material. Includes historical accounts of various university departments written by others and which did not appear in the published version.
University of Arizona -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Business and Public Administration -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Education -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Engineering -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Fine Arts -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Law -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Liberal Arts -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Mines -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Pharmacy -- History; University of Arizona -- Graduate College -- History; University of Arizona -- School of Home Economics -- History; University of Arizona -- College of Nursing -- History; University of Arizona -- Faculty; University of Arizona -- Library -- History; University of Arizona -- Dept. of Military Science and Tactics -- History; University of Arizona -- Dept. of Health, Physical Education and Recreation -- History; University of Arizona -- Dept. of Physical Education for Women -- History; Steward Observatory -- History; University of Arizona -- Student Union -- History; University of Arizona -- Alumni Association -- History; Interviews; Manuscripts; Sound recordings
Container List
- Series I: Manuscript Drafts, 1960
  - Author's original drafts. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration comments re: manuscript. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes and interviews. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni reminiscences. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Publicity. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Notes from Board of Regents: minutes. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Final typed copy. 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Printer's copy. 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series II: Audiotapes and Transcripts, 1958-1960
  - Tape records of persons interviews, with transcripts. 1958-1960 (Box 3)
- Series III: Historical Accounts, 1958-1960
  - College of Agriculture (missing). 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - College of Business and Public Administration. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - College of Education. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - College of Engineering. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - College of Fine Arts. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - College of Law. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - College of Liberal Arts. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - College of Mines. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - College of Pharmacy. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate College. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - School of Home Economiocs. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - School of Nursing. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bureaus, Laboratories, Institutes, etc. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faculty. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fraternities and Sororities. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Library. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Military Training. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Physical Education (Men): athletics. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Physical Education (Women). 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Steward Observatory. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Union. 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)